<?xml version="1.0"?>
<wayfire>
	<plugin name="workarounds">
		<_short>Workarounds</_short>
		<_long>Some hacks that might be required to make things work.</_long>
		<category>Utility</category>
		<option name="app_id_mode" type="string">
			<_short>Application ID mode</_short>
			<_long>Specifies the application ID mode.</_long>
			<default>stock</default>
			<desc>
				<value>stock</value>
				<_name>Stock</_name>
			</desc>
			<desc>
				<value>gtk-shell</value>
				<_name>GTK Shell</_name>
			</desc>
			<desc>
				<value>full</value>
				<_name>Full</_name>
			</desc>
		</option>
		<option name="all_dialogs_modal" type="bool">
			<_short>Make all dialogs modal</_short>
			<_long>If false, the main window can be focused even if it has a dialog. The dialog is nevertheless kept on top of the main window. Kwin defaults to false.</_long>
			<default>true</default>
		</option>
    <option name="dynamic_repaint_delay" type="bool">
      <_short>Allow dynamic repaint delay</_short>
      <_long>If true, allows Wayfire to dynamically recalculate its max_render_time, i.e allow render time higher than max_render_time.</_long>
      <default>false</default>
    </option>
    <option name="use_external_output_configuration" type="bool">
      <_short>Use external output configuration instead of Wayfire's own.</_short>
      <_long>If true, Wayfire will not handle any configuration options for outputs in the config file once an
      external daemon like https://github.com/emersion/kanshi sets the output configuration via the wlr-output-management protocol.
      Exceptions are made for options not available via wlr-output-management, like output mirroring and custom modelines.</_long>
      <default>false</default>
    </option>
    <option name="remove_output_limits" type="bool">
      <_short>Allow views to overlap between multiple outputs. Many of the core plugins will not behave properly with this option set!</_short>
      <default>false</default>
    </option>
    <option name="force_preferred_decoration_mode" type="bool">
      <_short>Force xdg-decoration clients to use the compositor-preferred decoration mode regardless of the client's preference.</_short>
      <default>false</default>
    </option>
    <option name="enable_so_unloading" type="bool">
      <_short>Enable calling dlclose() when a plugin is unloaded. Note that this may not work well with all plugins.</_short>
      <default>false</default>
    </option>
    <option name="discard_command_output" type="bool">
      <_short>Discard output from commands invoked by Wayfire, so that they don't end up in the logs.</_short>
      <default>true</default>
    </option>
	</plugin>
</wayfire>
